# — JORDAN ALEXIS ←

## CONTACT



646-625-8972



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jordan-alexis-

799214175/



alexisjordan842@gmail.com



https://jordan721.github.io/Central Site/

#### **PROFILE**

Hello, I'm a Junior Programmer and Designer and what that means for you is that I can not only program websites, video games, and computer networks I can also make digital arts for any occasion.

I have many years of learning about how the field of my occupation works. I have used many applications at my disposal to create graphic arts like Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, XD and Illustrator.

Using different programming languages, I publish websites on GitHub, Wix, WordPress and use these programming languages to create and/or program games on Unity, GameMaker, Maya, Unreal Engine.

## COMPUTER SKILLS

Intermediate Knowledge of Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, and XD.

Understanding and Translating computer data, proficiency in cloud computing, IT, basic audio production.

Intermediate knowledge of creating and designing websites.

Intermediate skills in Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.

Intermediate knowledge using Social Media.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Spring Intern, WBAI Radio, Brooklyn NY

January 2019 - May 2019

Assisted in Sorting and Mailing out prizes for their WBAI Buddies.

Managed their Social Media Using Hootsuite

Assigned in managing some Customer Service tasks.

Assisted in their event calendar by using Photoshop to make the pictures for each article presentable.

Assisted in entering important personal data for their WBAI Buddies.

## Multimedia Internship, SYEP, The Challenge Publisher Group, Brooklyn NY

July 2018 – August 2018

Assisted in creating a modernized version of a newspaper called "The New American" by making it in Adobe InDesign from scratch.

Used Photoshop to make images given to me more presentable.

Distributed the Newspaper to the boroughs of New York.

## Multimedia Developer Internship, SYEP, St. John's Recreation Center, Brooklyn NY

July 2017 - August 2017

Learned about Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign effectively.

Learned how to record audio using GarageBand and using audio to create a 3-5minute video using Windows Media Player.

### **EDUCATION**

## **Brooklyn College**

2019 - 2023

Bachelor's in Science, Major: Multimedia Computing and Computer Systems

# Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC), Manhattan, NY

2017 - 2019

Associate's in Science, Major: Multimedia Programming and Design

## **Technical Career Institute (TCI)**,

Manhattan, NY

2017-2017

Credits towards Networking Technology Degree

# **Bramson Ort College,** Queens NY

2014 - 2017

Credits towards Computer Information Systems: Major Game Design

## Day Care Worker, SYEP, Charles Churn Christian Academy, Brooklyn NY

July 2014 – August 2014

Assisted making sure the children (5-10) went to their destinations safely. Assisted in making activities, organized the work and camp environment. Carried equipment to wherever they needed to be.